<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on aryamans.me</title><link>https://aryaman73.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on aryamans.me</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 05:59:05 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aryaman73.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>_Why Day, and a really old MS-DOS project</title><link>https://aryaman73.github.io/posts/why-day/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 05:59:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://aryaman73.github.io/posts/why-day/</guid><description>Happy _why day! I learned about Why the Lucky Stiff when I was looking for resources to learn Ruby for my upcoming internship. Though I don&amp;rsquo;t really understand much of what made _why popular, I do understand his love for writing code for the sake of it - something I don&amp;rsquo;t feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing enough of. So, I thought today might be the day I dust off a really old DOS project I worked on way back in 2018, and see if I can still run it.</description></item><item><title>React Zendesk, and components that lie</title><link>https://aryaman73.github.io/posts/react-zendesk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 22:34:48 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://aryaman73.github.io/posts/react-zendesk/</guid><description>Zendesk is a very popular cloud-based customer service platform that lets you implement chatbots and CRM systems easily - but you probably recognize them from these buttons at the bottom-right of many websites:
If you’ve ever wanted to implement this on a React app, you’ve probably encountered React Zendesk, which attempts to convert Zendesk&amp;rsquo;s widget into a React Component. It has over 10k weekly downloads and a bunch of references online, but it is far from official.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://aryaman73.github.io/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 22:59:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://aryaman73.github.io/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to start a technical-but-not-really blog for a while, partially to increase my ✨ web presence ✨, but mostly to create a space for me to talk about things I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about. If not for others to read, but for me to look back on.
Behind this post was hours of deciding and researching between Jekyll, Gatsby, and Hugo. Jekyll is old and mature and uses Ruby, which is a language I&amp;rsquo;m trying to learn as part of my co-op.</description></item><item><title>My UWaterloo Story (Year 1)</title><link>https://aryaman73.github.io/posts/my-uwaterloo-story-year-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 22:59:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://aryaman73.github.io/posts/my-uwaterloo-story-year-1/</guid><description>This is meant to be a summary of my time at the University of Waterloo. I was admitted to the Computer Engineering program in Fall 2019, and my (expected) graduation year is 2024. I was inspired to write this after reading Jonathan Tsang&amp;rsquo;s story, and I&amp;rsquo;ll be adding to it as time goes on.
(This post was written way before I created this blog, but I am only getting around to editing and posting it now.</description></item></channel></rss>